netnation.com 2006-06-13

# NetNation - TERMS OF USE

NetNation Communications Inc. ("NetNation") respects the privacy of its customers and visitors and is committed to protecting the personal information of its customers and visitors. This Privacy Policy covers the site [www.netnation.com ](http://www.netnation.com/). We collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit our site unless you choose to provide that information to us or as specifically outlined in this Policy. This Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use ("TOU") Agreement found at [http://www.netnation.com/company/terms.php ](http://www.netnation.com/company/terms.php). 

This Policy describes our general principles for the collection and use of information from customers and visitors to our Web sites. We want to ensure that you understand how we will and will not use the information you entrust to us. In order to fully understand your rights we encourage you to read this Policy. 

For visitors, we've structured our Web sites so that, in general, you can visit us on Web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. 

For prospective and existing customers and partners, once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it will only be used to support your relationship with NetNation. 

**What type of information does NetNation collect?**

When you visit our Web site, our Web server collects basic user information about you that includes your ISP's domain, the time you accessed our Web site, and the pages from within our Web site that you visit and is not personally identifiable information except as needed to prevent fraud or abuse of the system. 

When you sign up for NetNation's services, you provide us with both contact and payment information. Contact information typically includes your name, address, and phone number. Payment information typically includes your credit card number. 

While you are a NetNation customer, we manage information with regard to your account status, choice of services, and customer logs. In addition, we may store customers' electronic mail and other communications as a necessary incident to the transmission and delivery of those communications. 

NetNation does not trade, rent or sell your personal information to any other organization or third party. 

We use the contact information you provide us to establish our service for you. We use payment information for payment processing purposes only. We create and maintain other information such as customer account status, choice of services, and customer logs in the normal course of providing service. By pressing the "submit" button, each visitor constitutes consent to use the information for purposes stated in this Policy. 

NetNation may share customer information with selected partners/third parties, for example, to provide you with information about products which might be of interest to you or to enable you to take advantage of special partner programs. NetNation may also use customer information to provide customers with system information or information about new or upgraded products if you have chosen to receive such offers. Customers may opt out of receiving information about partner/third party promotional emails from NetNation by sending a request to [partnerprograms-unsubscribe@netnation.com ](mailto:partnerprograms-unsubscribe@netnation.com). 

Our trusted affiliates are responsible for processing or handling some of the information we receive, such as order fulfillment for domain name registration. Those affiliates are not authorized to use such information for purposes beyond those specified by us and are required to preserve the confidentiality with which we treat such information. 

We may disclose contact information with your permission when gathering and posting testimonials. 

We will not otherwise disclose customer personal and account information unless we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, make contact with, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing harm or interfering with the rights or property of NetNation, our customers, or others. We may provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable laws or where NetNation has a good faith belief that the law requires such disclosure. 

NetNation also will not disclose to third parties the contents of any electronic mail or other electronic communications that NetNation stores or transmits for its customers except where: (a) it is a matter or public safety or policy; (b) it is in connection with the transfer of other business assets; (c) i t is required to cooperate with orders, warrants, or other legal process that NetNation determines in its sole discretion to be valid and enforceable; and (d) i t is necessary to provide to a law enforcement agency when the contents are inadvertently obtained by NetNation and appear to pertain to the commission of a crime. 

NetNation disclaims any intention to censor, edit, or engage in ongoing review or surveillance of communications stored on or transmitted through its facilities by customers or others. NetNation will, however, review, delete, or block access to communications that may harm NetNation, its customers or third parties. The grounds on which NetNation may take such action include, but are not limited to, actual or potential violations of the TOU. 

Please note that NetNation may use this information collected to direct notices as well as provide you with other general information that may be of interest to you and information about our services or product offerings or the offerings of our business affiliates, as well as other important information regarding your account or services at our discretion. 

Customers may opt out of receiving newsletters and/or promotional emails from NetNation by sending a request to [newsletter-unsubscribe@netnation.com ](mailto:newsletter-unsubscribe@netnation.com). In this request, customers must identify their domain name and contact information. Customers may not opt out of receiving information from NetNation which is essential for maintaining or updating customers account or system information. 

**Third Party Advertising and Cookies**

The basic user information collected is used to help us analyze Web traffic, improve the content of our Web site and improve your experience on our Web site. 

We do not trade, rent or sell your personal information to others, except as detailed in this Policy .  We currently contract with several online partners who use the data only on our behalf to help manage and optimize our Internet business and communications. We use the services of a marketing company to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site. To do this, we use Action Tags and cookies provided by our marketing company on this site. The information collected by the marketing company through the use of Action Tags and cookies is not personally identifiable.  The information we collect helps us learn things like what kinds of customers our site attracts, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Although our marketing company logs the information coming from our site on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used. 

We may at times also use cookies, which are small pieces of information that a Web site can store in a designated file on your computer. Cookies allow a Web application to respond to you as an individual. By gathering and remembering information about your preferences, the Web application can tailor its operation to your needs, likes, and dislikes. Most web browsers allow you to control this use of cookies. Please take a look at your particular browser for instructions on this function. If you elect to disable cookies, please keep in mind that you will not be able to take full advantage of a personalized experience on our Web site. It is possible that some portions of the site will not function properly or may perform more slowly if you choose to reject cookies. 

Our Web site allows for a chat function. Chat functions allow you to participate in "live" online conversations with us on our Web site. Although the transcripts from the chats may be stored internally on in-house servers for our records only, we collect no personally identifiable information about you when you participate unless you choose to provide that information to us. 

**How Can I access my personal information?**

You can access your personal information, such as your address and contact information, at anytime to correct or change any of the data shared with us when you became a customer of NetNation. As a customer of NetNation you can access your personal information by clicking on the "Customer Login" link at the top of any Web page. Your account information is secure and is accessible by using a password that you select. If you need assistance or have questions about correcting information you can contact us via email at [cs@netnation.com ](mailto:cs@netnation.com). 

**Security**

NetNation has security measures in place to help prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. When you place an order online, your information, including your credit card number, is protected using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology. This encrypts order data and is designed to aid in ensuring the accuracy and security of that customer information. 

**Links**

Our Web site provides links to other Web sites, sites that may be maintained by companies that are not affiliates of ours. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites and we encourage you to use caution. In particular, we recommend that you view the privacy policy posted on each site to confirm the sites policies are acceptable to you. This Policy applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

NetNation does not sell products or services for purchase by children. Customers must be at least 18 years of age. Any individual under the age of 18 ("Minor") must have a parent or guardian accept the TOU in order for the Minor to become a Customer. If you are under 18, we strongly encourage you to use our Web site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

**Changes to our Policy**

NetNation reserves the right to change this Policy simply by posting such changes on our site. We encourage you to periodically check our site for changes to this Policy since your continued use of the site following any changes to this Policy will be deemed to constitute your acceptance of such change. The operative and effective version of this Policy will be the latest version available on the site. 

You may opt out of any posted changes to our collection, use or disclosure of your personal information by sending an email to [privacy@netnation.com ](mailto:privacy@netnation.com). In this request, customers must identify their domain name and contact information. 

**Contact Us**

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, you should contact us by email at [privacy@netnation.com ](mailto:privacy@netnation.com).
